# MAKSYM TSYBULSKYI DEVOPS/SRE

Sacramento, CA 95842 · 916-578-86-78 tomahawksmail@gmail · LinkedIn Profile · GitHub

#### SUMMARY

I am an engineer with over 15 years of experience in IT. In total more than 12 years held the position of head of the IT department. My main qualities are self-management, responsibility and time-management. I always try to work for the result. I have completed a DevOps engineering course and I want to find a new job. I am always happy to learn something new and share my knowledge among my colleagues.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# 12/2012 - 03/2022 **HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT/ARCHITECT**

**CLINIC OF SAINT CATHERINE** UKRAINE, ODESA

- Management of the IT department team, its rallying and focusing on
- Install and maintain multiple virtualized services in the cloud and on your own server fleet
- Automation and optimization of processes using Python
- Development of a system (Python3+Flask) for call statistics in a call center (FreePBX)
- Construction and maintenance of IT infrastructure of the enterprise
- Development of regulations for interaction with the IT department
- Hosting and domain management, zone setup, mail server administration (8 domains)

## 05/2010 - 10/2012 **HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT**

**CHAIN OF RETAIL STORES "VIRTUS"** 

UKRAINE, ODESA

- Construction and maintenance of IT infrastructure of the enterprise

01/2006 - 06/2010 **CHIEF ENGINEER** 

**SECURITY SYSTEMS INTEGRATOR** 

"AGENT-SB" UKRAINE, ODESA

**EDUCATION** 

2000 - 2006**ODESSA NATIONAL** 

**TELECOMMUNICATIONS ACADEMY** BY O.S.POPOV UKRAINE, ODESA

-Design and installation of security systems

**BACHELOR, Information Communication Networks** 

## COURSES & CERTIFICATES

02/2022 HILLEL IT school DevOps 12/2021 AWS TECHNICAL ESSENTIALS 01/2023 AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials 01/2022 TP-LINK CERTIFIED PARTNER

01/2023 AWS Networking Basics

#### SKILLS

- Linux: Ubuntu, Debian
- MS Windows Server: AD, DNS, GPO, SMB
- Networking: Subnetting, TCP, UDP, HTTP(S), IPSec
- IaC: Terraform
- SQL: MySQL (MariaDB), MS SQL Server
- Scripts: Python3
- Version Control System: Git, GitHub
- Containers: Docker, Docker Compose
- Clouds: AWS VPC, AWS CLI
- Configuration Management: Ansible
- Virtualization: VMware, Oracle VM Virtual Box, Vagrant

### Basic skills

- CI/CD: Jenkins, Git Lab, GitHub
- Scripts: Bash
- Web server: NGINX
- Orchestration: Kubernetes, Docker Swarm
- Observability: Logging with ELK Stack
- WSGI: Gunicorn+Flask
- Synchronization: Rsync